mikelitman.com 2013-12-28

# 

mikelitman.com
Privacy Policy
Effective Date: July, 2012
The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of Mikelitman.com. ("we" or
"us"). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using the
mikelitman.com the "Site"), and the ways in which we use this information. This Privacy Policy, including
our children's privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may
collect offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail).
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site,
and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy. Because the Web is an evolving medium,
we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we'll post the changes
to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the
changes. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as
modified.
How We Collect and Use Information
We may collect and store personal or other information that you voluntarily supply to us online while using
the Site (e.g., while on the Site or in responding via email to a feature provided on the Site). This site only
contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so or in the event that they have signed up to
receive our free newsletters or have purchased one of our products. This site collects personally identifying
information from our users during online registration and online purchasing. Generally, this information
includes name and e-mail address for registration to receive our free newsletters and name, postal address,
and credit card information when purchasing our products. All of this information is provided to us by you.
We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate online through the
Site. For example, we may collect information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which
allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on the
Site. We also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a "cookie" to enhance your
experience with the Site. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-
keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us deliver advertisements,
identify how many unique users visit us, and track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from
having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the Site where you may have entered preference
information before. The Site also may use web beacons (single-pixel graphic files also known as
"transparent GIFs") to access cookies and to count users who visit the Site or open HTML-formatted email
messages.
We use the information we collect from you while you are using the Site in a variety of ways, including using
the information to customize features. and advertising that appear on the Site. We also may provide your
information to third parties, such as marketing partners, service providers and contractors for a variety of
purposes. Unless you inform us in accordance with the process described below, we reserve the right to
use, and to disclose to third parties, all of the information collected from and about you while you are using
the Site in any way and for any purpose, such as to enable us or a third party to provide you with information
about products and services. If you do not wish your information to be used for these purposes, you must
send a letter to the Online Privacy Coordinator whose address is listed at the end of this Privacy Policy
requesting to be taken off any lists of information that may be used for these purposes or that may be given
or sold to third-parties.
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by
third parties online - for example on message boards, web logs, through email, or in chat areas - that
information can be seen, collected and used by others besides us. We cannot be responsible for any
unauthorized third-party use of such information.

Some of our third-party advertisers and ad servers that place and present advertising on the Site also may
collect information from you via cookies, web beacons or similar technologies. These third-party advertisers
and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure
and research the advertisements' effectiveness, or for other purposes. The use and collection of your
information by these third-party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third-party's privacy
policy and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. Indeed, the privacy policies of these third-party advertisers
and ad servers may be different from ours. If you have any concerns about a third party's use of cookies or
web beacons or use of your information, you should visit that party's website and review its privacy policy.
The Site also includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third
parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third-party
products or services through the Site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of
the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.
We may also make some content, products and services available through our Site through cooperative
relationships with third-party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the Site in
connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any
information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in
cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you
directly, in which cases the privacy policy of our provider partner may apply to the provider partner's use of
your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions
regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider partner directly
for more information.
Be aware that we may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to
comply with law or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of the Site or the public.
Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we
sell some or all of our assets, or one or more of our websites is acquired by another company, information
about our users may be among the transferred assets.
Children's Privacy Statement
This children's privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of
personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information regarding
their rights under federal law with respect to such information.
          This Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do NOT knowingly collect
           personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site. We
           screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of
           thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received
           personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we will
           delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain
           prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from
           children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site.
          Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of
           thirteen as part of the Site, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
          We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise
           distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Site.
          Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of
           thirteen as part of the Site, we do NOT condition the participation of a child under thirteen in the
           Site's online activities on providing personally identifiable information.
How do we store your information?

Your information is stored at the list server that delivers mikelit.com emails and data. Your information can
only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those who would like to
receive mikelitman.com data.
All of the emails that are sent to you by mikelitman.com include an unsubscribe link in them. You can
remove yourself at any time from our newsletters or mailing list by clicking on the unsubscribe link that can
be found in every cmmunicaiton that we send you...
Disclaimer
Although it is highly unlikely, This policy may be changed at any time at our discretion. If we should update
this policy, we will post the updates to this page on our Website.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please direct them to :
Info@mikelitman.com
